Sakura-chan, what are you doing lately?
さくらちゃん、最近何してるの?
Recently, I went to an idol concert.
最近はアイドルのライブに行きました
Idol live?
ア イドルのライブ?
You like idols.
アイドル好きなんだね
You look cute today too.
今日も可愛いね
As always.
相変わらず
Which live performance was fun?
楽しかったそのライブは?
It was fun.
楽しかったね
Will it go quite far?
結構遠くまで行くの?
Once in a while.
たまには
Yeah.
うん
So, did you get a boyfriend?
で、彼氏はできた?
I can't.
できない
Can't you?
できないの?
Don't men and people play?
男と人は遊んでないの?
I'm not playing.
遊んでないです
No dates?
デートとかもなし?
yes.
そう
It's a waste.
もったいないね
So how many people have experience?
じゃあ経験人数は?
Isn't it increasing?
増えてない?
No change.
変わらない
Has it remained the same?
変わらずか
It feels like only one person is updating once again.
また一人だけ、一回更新しちゃう感じになるね
That uniform suits you too.
その制服も似合うね
How was it when you tried it last time?
前回やってみてどうだった?
I was nervous, but it was fun.
緊張したけど、楽しかった
it was fun?
楽しかった?
It was a new page, right?
新たなページだったでしょ
Have you done anything summery lately?
最近夏らしいことした?
I'm going to the pool.
プール行くんだね
it was fun?
楽しかった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
Was there a lazy river?
流れるプールとかあった?
Good then.
じゃあよかったね
Well then, Sakura-chan, please stand there.
じゃあ桜ちゃん、そこ立ってみて
It's small today too.
今日もちっちゃいね
He's not 150cm tall.
150センチないもんね
Look back.
後ろ向いてみ
Try raising that maskato.
そのマスカート上げてみて
A cute person came in today as well.
今日も可愛い人に入ってきたね
Look at me with your face.
顔でこっちを見て
Look at me.
こっちを見て
Kuro-chan, go next door.
黒ちゃん、隣に行って
Well then, let's take a look at Sakura-chan's body today too.
じゃあ今日も桜ちゃんの体見ちゃおうか
Can I run it?
流せていい?
It's cute underneath.
下で可愛いな
English drunk.
英語酔っぱい
It's okay, Sakura-chan.
いいよ、桜ちゃん
Below too.
下も
I really like the style.
超スタイルいいね
Is your chest too big?
胸もでっか
How many cups?
何カップだっけ?
E cup.
Eカップ
I have an E cup.
Eカップあるんだ
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Your ass, try to dig into your pants.
お尻さ、パンツ食い込ましてみて
Sakura-chan.
桜ちゃん
So turn over here.
それでこっち向いてほら
Stick out your butt.
お尻プリって突き出して
cute?
可愛い?
this.
これ
It's so erotic.
すごいエロいね
Sakura-chan, please touch my butt.
桜ちゃん、お尻触ってみ
Turn into a butt.
お尻に変わってみ
copper?
どう?
What about an 18 year old's butt?
18歳のお尻は?
Is it chewy?
もちもちしてる?
There has to be a change in the cracks.
その割れ目のところに変わってないと
Sakura-chan, how do you feel about being in a perverted space for the first time in a while?
桜ちゃん、久しぶりの変態空間どう?
My heart is pounding.
ドキドキする
Are you excited?
ドキドキする?
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いよ
Sakura-chan, wet your pants.
桜ちゃん、パンツ濡らして
Big butt.
大きいお尻
It's true.
本当だ
Why did you get wet?
なんで濡れちゃったの?
Did you get wet?
濡れちゃったの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's been a while since we did something naughty and fell asleep right away.
久しぶりエッチなことしてすぐ寝れちゃったんだよ
What a naughty girl.
エッチな子だな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Sakura-chan, you want to take that home with you, right?
桜ちゃん、それ持って帰りたいでしょ
I also wore a bra.
ブラジャーもしたぞ
remove.
外す
Those are amazing boobs.
すごいおっぱいだね
Even though it's a loli-loli face.
ロリロリの顔なのに
She's got bigger breasts than an adult, right?
おっぱいだけ大人より立派なのつけてるでしょ
Erotic body.
エロい体
What do you like most about your body?
自分の体で一番好きなところはどこ?
Is it the waist?
ウエストか
You're so constricted.
めっちゃくびれてるもんね
You have abdominal muscles.
腹筋あるよね
There's a little bit.
ちょっとある
He has a muscular, somewhat erotic body.
筋肉質、なんかエロい体してるわ
Sakura-chan, just touch it.
桜ちゃん、じゃあ触っちゃってそれ
copper?
どう?
What about Sakura's breasts?
桜ちゃんのおっぱいは?
Even if you get caught?
挟まれても?
Sakura-chan, go ahead and hold Sakura-chan's face with your hands.
桜ちゃん、自分でさ、手で桜ちゃんの顔挟んであげてよ
Also, rub the chikubi.
あと、チクビをこすりつけて
By yourself.
自分で
copper?
どう?
My boobs are licked.
おっぱい舐められて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Look here.
こっち見てごらん
So cute.
すんげー可愛い
You're being teased a lot.
チクビいじられちゃってんね
hey.
ね
You've stood up amazingly.
すげー立ってきたでしょ
Do you understand?
わかる?
By yourself.
自分で
Are you standing stiffly?
チクビ立ってんの
Do you understand?
わかるの?
Why is it hard?
なんで固くなるの?
that.
それ
I can feel it.
感じちゃう
When it feels good, it gets hard.
気持ちいいと固くなるんだ
Naughty body.
エッチな体
Sakura-chan, don't say the opposite.
桜ちゃん、反対を喋りな
Well, let's go gradually to the bottom.
じゃあ、だんだん下の方に行ってごらん
Let me lick that pussy.
そのまんすじ舐めてあげて
delicious?
おいしい?
Sakura-chan.
桜ちゃん
Were you wet?
濡れちゃってた?
Would you like to put your right foot up there?
右足そこにあげてみる?
There.
そこに
Yes, high up.
そう、高いところに
Can you give it to me?
あげれる?
So, Sakura-chan, wait.
で、桜ちゃん、待って
Tiny pussy.
ちっちゃいまんこ
Open up more, Sakura-chan.
もっと、桜ちゃん、開いて
You can see deep into the hole.
穴の奥まで見えるよ
Let me lick that pussy.
そのまんすじ舐めてあげて
Chestnut, I want to mess with it.
くり、いじったいな
Put your tongue in the hole.
穴に舌入れて
What if your pussy gets wet?
おまんこ濡れてきたら?
Sakura-chan, put your hands over there.
桜ちゃん、あっちに4つんばやって
Butt here.
お尻こっち
Stick it out more and give it a try.
もっと突き出して、ぶりって
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Erotic.
えろ
It's so sexy.
めっちゃえろいね
Hey, look this way.
ほら、こっち向いて
Better face it.
顔向けたほうが
Sakura-chan, open your pussy.
桜ちゃん、おまんこ開いて
It's a tiny pussy, really.
ちっちゃいおまんこだな、本当に
Sakura-chan.
桜ちゃん
I wish I could just lick that ass.
そのままお尻舐めたらいいな
Open it.
開いて
Open it and take a look.
開いて見して
show me.
見せて
Look this way.
こっち向いて
What about your butt hole?
お尻の穴どう?
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
Perop.
ペロップ
Pussy and all.
おまんこも全部
Sakura-chan's voice is naughty.
桜ちゃん、声エッチだね
Show me your open pussy.
おまんこの穴開いてる顔見せて
Do you have such a cute face?
こんな可愛い顔してるの?
Sakura-chan, put it inside.
桜ちゃん、下の中に入れて
It even includes Itch-Mank.
イッチマンクまで入ってるぞ、それ
Put it all in.
全部入れて
Finally, spread it out.
最後、広げて
Both holes are erotic, this one.
穴2つともエロいね、これ
Even the ketuan is included.
ケツアンさえも入れて
Ru.
る
Erotic pussy.
え ろいまんこ
With chestnut hair.
栗の髪で
Sakura-chan.
桜ちゃん
Sit here.
ここに座ってね
In the gymnastics seat.
体操座に
Even if you open it.
開いても
Have your butt rubbed earlier.
お尻もっと前にすぎはしてもらう
Open more.
もっと開いて
Perop.
ペロップ
Chestnut is standing.
栗立ってるよ
Try cutting it with your finger.
指で切ってみてくれよ
Are you always there?
いつもそこいじるの?
Same time.
同じ時
Let me see
見せてごらん
well.
じゃ
Amazing erotic pussy.
すごい エロいまんこの
It's getting wet inside.
中濡れてきてるよ
The chestnuts are getting bigger.
栗大きくなってきたね
Let's peel it off.
剥いてみよう
It takes standing up.
立ってんのかかるでしょ
Can I use a feeling toy?
気持ちおもちゃ使っていい?
To Sakura-chan and Goranshi-san.
桜ちゃん、ごらんしさんに
Sakura-chan, cunt Chloela.
桜ちゃん、おまんクロエラ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I want you to show me your pleasant face.
気持ちいい顔いっぱい見せてもらう
Try cutting it with your finger.
指で切ってみて
Since then, my butt has always been cut.
そ こからいつも尻が切ってるね
Sakura-chan, try putting your foot on this.
桜ちゃん、この上に足置いてみて
This one too.
こっちも
So come earlier.
それでもっと前にきて
Cut until you can cut it with your feet.
足で切るまで切って
Your pussy Chloela is so slippery.
おまんクロエラ、ぬるぬるじゃん
That's fine
そんでいい
Yo.
よ
Sakura-chan, try calling Sakura-chan as well.
桜 ちゃん、桜ちゃんに電話も出してみて
I'm forgetting how I feel about this.
これで自分の気持ちで忘れてる
Let me see it.
見せてもらう
Chloella has feelings.
気 持ちおもんクロエラ
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいいの?
Have a lot of surprises.
いっぱいスイスイしてもらう
Pussy Chloela, try twitching.
おまんクロエラ、ひくひくしてみて
Try cutting it again with your finger.
また指で切ってみて
It means ojiku.
おじくってこと
Even if you touch it all, it will become red bean paste.
全部触ってもあんこになってくる
All faces will be revealed.
全部の面相が出るんだよ
I stood around.
立ち回した
A manju came out.
まんじゅる出てきた
I say it when I feel like saying it.
言っちゃいそうなとき言うんだよ
Don't just say it.
勝手に言っちゃダメだよ
I'm talking a lot.
ぐちゃぐちゃ言ってる
Are you feeling better?
気持ちよくなってきた?
Manjuru is amazing.
すごいよ、まんじゅるは
I feel like I'm going to say it.
言っちゃいそうなの
Hold on to your limits.
限界まで我慢して
Chloe Ella, cunt Chloe Ella.
ク ロ エラ、おまんクロエラ
I'm not going anywhere.
行くとこにしてない
Wipe.
ふいてん
I don't tack on it quickly at all.
全然さっさとタッカキしないじゃん、
Pussy Chloela.
おまんクロエラ
Cloella, futen.
クロエラ、ふいてん
Wipe.
ふいてん
Do it again, try it again.
もう一回やって、もう一回
Chloela, take that.
クロエラ、それ、持ってさ
Try going inside.
中入るか実験してみて
Is it okay?
いいのかな?
It's tough, after all.
きついな、やっぱりです
I swallowed.
飲み込んだ
It's hitting me hard.
ぶっ刺さってる
Drop it slowly.
ゆっくり落として
It's swallowing my whole head.
頭全部飲み込んじゃってる
Pull it out slowly and stab it.
ゆっくり抜き刺して
My pussy is getting stuck.
まんこがひっついてくるね
It's so big that it can fit inside.
こんなでっかいの入っちゃうんだ
Amazing little
すごいちっちゃ
stomach.
い
It stung me.
刺 さっちゃったね
It's too tight and won't come out.
きつすぎて出てこない
Take a look at the end.
最後見てみ
It's tough there.
きついよ、そこ
Well done, look at the size.
よくやって、サイズから見てみ
Chloe, turn that around.
クロエラ、それ回して
I'm going to go into this big place.
このでっかちに入るよ
amazing.
すごい
I don't act like this.
こんなぶってないんだ
Does it hit deep?
奥まで当たってる?
That's right.
当たってる
It's so tight that the machine stops inside.
きつすぎて中で機械止まっちゃうね
What kind of pussy did you teach?
おまんこどんな感じで教えた?
Do you understand?
わかる?
How about that?
それがどうなの?
Please pull it out and stab it.
抜き刺してね
Wow, you've swallowed the size.
すげえ、サイズ飲み込んでんじゃん
Take your legs out more.
もっと足を抜いて
Pull it out and pull it out properly.
抜いてちゃんと抜いて
Pull it out and stab it.
抜き刺して
That insect you pulled out.
抜いたあの虫
I cried so hard.
こんなでっかい泣いちゃった
Pisson please.
ピッソンしてね
Stop the one on the left.
左のやつ止めて
Finally, do a pisson from here.
最後、こっからピッソンして
It's big enough to fit into pressure points.
ツボとか入るね、でっかい
Your pussy is perverted, Saglaja.
おまんこ変態だな、サグラジャー
Chloela-chan, aren't you being licked anymore?
クロエラちゃん、もう舐められてない?
Ching Ching?
チンチン?
Touch my pants too.
パンツもやっぱ触って
Is it still soft?
まだ柔らかい?
What are you touching now?
今どこ触ってんの?
Tip?
先っぽ?
So why don't you try looking for those pants?
じゃあそれパンツ探してみしてみる?
It smells good,
匂いがいいぞ、
that.
それ
What does it smell like?
ど んな匂いするの?
There is a smell of picken.
ピッケンの匂いがある
Didn't you smell dick?
チンチンの匂いしなかった?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Chloela-chan, make that face.
クロエラちゃん、それ顔はして
more
もっと
Make it into your teeth.
歯 にしちゃって
Peti pechi.
ぺちぺち
Opposition.
反対
The whole face.
顔全部
Open your mouth.
口開けて
Eat.
食べて
You're so big, Chin Chin.
おっきいね、チンチン
Yeah, it's big.
うん、おっきい
There's only the tip in there, right?
先っぽしか入ってないでしょ
I need you to try harder.
も っと頑張ってくれないと
Awesome.
すんごい
There is also drool.
よだれもある
Chloe, let me play.
クロエラちゃん、しゃぐらせて
Eat a lot.
いっぱい食べて
That's the way to go, right?
それ手でしょしょ
It's hard, isn't it?
硬いでしょ
hard.
硬い
Eat a lot.
いっぱい食べて
Tasty, chin chin.
味わいな、チンチン
Show me a little.
ちょっと見せて
What are you going to do about that?
それどうすんの?
It's hard to put on, isn't it?
つ けてしこしこでしょ
It's huge, Chin Chin.
でっかいよ、チンチン
Eat all of Cali.
カリ全部食べて
I could go all the way.
あっとうくまでいけて
Look at the person who was having fun.
しゃぐった方こっち見て
Kito is sloppy.
きとうぺろぼろして
Suck it slowly.
じぼじぼ吸って
It's better to lick dick
チンチン舐めてる方がいい
Yo.
よ
Finally, let's make Chloe stand up one more time.
最後、 もう一回クロエラちゃん立っておこう
Hold me in your arms.
手上抱えて
On hand.
手上
Hold Chloe's hand.
クロエラちゃん手を持って
If it feels good, I'll lick it a lot,
気持ちいいといっぱい舐めちゃうから、
Chloela-chan.
クロエラちゃん
I've been sucking on it since this morning.
今朝からしゃぶりついてた
Stay strong, Chloela-chan.
クロエラちゃん、しっかり
Let's suck more, that day.
もっといっぱいしゃぶれな、その1日
Is it painful?
苦しいの?
It's so ticking, so ticking.
すごいチンチン、カチカチだよ
You understand, right?
わかるでしょ?
You can stretch out your hand.
手を伸ばしていいよ
She has a very erotic face.
すごいエロい顔してる
Chloela-chan, look at this bed.
クロエラちゃん、このベッド見て
I'm so cursed, you know.
すごいのられついてるよ、ほら
I was sucking a lot of dick.
チンこいっぱいしゃぶってたもんね
Chloela-chan, lick your breasts again.
クロエラちゃん、またおっぱい舐めて
People are talking about my boobs even when they look at them.
おっぱい見てもしゃべられてる
Erotic, right?
エロいでしょ?
Chloela-chan, lick my armpits too.
クロエラちゃん、脇も舐めて
Lick all the sweat off.
汗全部舐めてあげな
Because I'm licking everything.
全部舐めましてるから
Chloela-chan, be free.
クロエラちゃん、自由に
Get your tongue out more.
もっとベロ出しな
Look this way.
こっち向いて
I'll put the pussy together.
おまんこまとめます
Chloela-chan, hold her legs and help yourself.
クロエラちゃん、足抱えて、自分で
Up to the asshole.
ケツの穴まで
Feel free to suck it all.
自由にしゃぶってみ、全部
Chloela-chan, put your finger in it.
クロエラちゃん、指入れて
Try rubbing it on the top where it feels good.
上の気持ちいいところ、擦ってみて
It's Bisubishu.
ビシュビシュじゃん
Turn it higher, properly.
もっと上に手回ししてね、ちゃんと
Scrape it out.
かき出してね
Chloe, come here now.
クロエラちゃん、もうこっちに
Can you suck my dick again?
また、チンチンしゃぶってもらえる?
It's stiff.
ガチガチだね
Samura-chan, please lick my thighs.
サムラちゃん、ももんこ舐めてもらえな
I hope you lick me a lot.
いっぱい舐めてもらえな
into the hole.
穴の中に
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
Can you lick me?
舐められるの?
like.
好き
Did you suck cock instead?
代わりにチンポしゃぶった?
I happened to drink it.
たまたま飲んで
Up to the butt.
お尻まで
I sucked it while jerking it with my hand.
手でシコシコしながらしゃぶって
Look at it with your hands.
手で見てみて
Just with your mouth.
口だけで
Look at it with your hands.
手で見てみて
Just suck it with your mouth.
口だけでしゃぶって
I lost my dick on tour.
ツアーでチンコめためた
Fore-chan, should I go in already?
フォアちゃん、もう入れちゃうか
amazing.
すごい
Squash.
くしょくしょ
What do you think, Kuro-chan?
どう、黒ちゃん?
It feels so good.
すっごい気持ちいい
do my best.
頑張る
Isn't your pussy tight?
マンコ、きついでしょ?
What's going on inside your pussy?
マンコの中でチンチン、どうなってる?
Kuro-chan, I have no choice but to listen to more strokes.
黒ちゃん、もっとストロークを聞くしかないです
It's so hot, pussy.
ピチャピチャいってるよ、マンコ
Next time, Samura-chan, bend your elbows down.
今度、サムラちゃん、下にひじって
Kuro-chan, be happy.
黒ちゃん、もんきして
There are a lot of manjiri.
まんじり、いっぱいついてるよ
背面基準
At the back.
後ろに
Chimp it yourself.
自分でチンプいれて
Hit it to the very root.
一番根元まで打ちつけて
Roll it there.
そこで巻いて
Nice trolling sound.
いい荒らし音
My pussy is so wet.
おマンコ、ビチャビチャじゃん
It's making a lot of noise, you know.
すんごい音してるよ、ほら
Eh, that sounds good.
えー、いい音が
It's dripping with juice.
汁たれちゃってるね
It's picha picha.
ピチャピチャだって
Times, MG.
次、MG
So, behind.
それで、後ろ
Get your hands behind me.
後ろに手ついて
Show me your pussy, where it's penetrated.
おマンコ、刺さってるとこ見せてほら
It's stabbing me, look.
ぶつ刺さってるよ、ふってほら
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
黒 ちゃん、だんだん早くして
Doesn't it feel good inside?
奥の気持ちいいでしょ?
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
黒ちゃん、もっと早く
I got confused again.
またブルブルしちゃったの
Go chimp.
チンプいって
Place both hands properly behind the back.
ちゃんと両方手ついて、後ろ
Kuro-chan, please breathe again.
黒ちゃん、また息をしてやって
Let's hold out until once.
1回まで我慢していこう
That hard cock feels so good.
硬いチンチン、気持ちいいんだ
Try removing it.
抜いてみしてごらんが
My pussy twitches.
おマンコ、ヒクヒク
I just did it.
い ったばっかり
Put it on your pillow like this.
こんな枕のところに入れて
Kuro-chan, put it on the side.
黒ちゃん、横に入れて
Can I have you come all the way inside?
奥まで入ってもらっていい?
Does that feel good?
そこが気持ちいい?
Man juice today.
マン汁だな、今日
Man juice, it's slimy, man juice.
マン汁、ぬるぐるになってるよ、マン汁
Let's make it normal.
正常にしよう
This pussy feels good, doesn't it?
気持ちいいでしょ、このマンコ
Kuro-chan, hold your legs.
黒ちゃん、足持って
I realized it now.
今、気づいたよな
Kuro-chan, put your feet up.
黒ちゃん、足上にして
Goods are stuck deep inside.
奥までグッズ刺さってるよ
Kuro-chan, let me cum a lot today too.
黒ちゃん、今日も中出しいっぱいして
You gave it all, Kuro-chan.
全部出したな、黒ちゃん
You gave it once, Kuro-chan.
1回出したな、黒ちゃん
Get up!
起き上がってごらん
It's full of pussy juice, so let's clean it up.
マン汁だらけだから、お掃除しとこ
Also use bell.
ベルも使って
I can't taste pussy anymore, what a pussy.
マンコの味しなくなる、マンコなんて
Was it beautifully done?
綺麗にできた?
You were cute today too, Sakura-chan.
今日も可愛かったね、さくらちゃん
how was it?
どうだった?
It felt so good.
どうも、気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Well then, I'll see you again next time.
じゃあ、また今度会ってくれるよね
Does that mean I'll go again?
また行っちゃうってこと?
Kiwarigato.
きわりがと
bye bye.
バイバイ